------------------------
   Sely GUMI　Ver1.01
 MikuMikuDance Model Data
------------------------
 \ This English translation is an summary of terms of use. Refer to the original Japanese text for more details.

 # Contents
   / sGUMI.pmx
   / sGUMI_sBONE.pmx
   / Texture
   / Hand_vpd（Pose-data）
   / readme.txt

 # Terms of Use
   / Use this model in accordance with the terms of service of INTERNET Co., Ltd. ,the copyright holder of this character.
      http://www.ssw.co.jp/products/vocal3/english_c_license/index.html

   / The newest thing is applied when terms of service are updated.
   / Read and agree with ALL terms of use written in this txt file before using this MikuMikuDance Model Data.
   / If you do not agree with all terms of use, or if you do not understand any part of this terms of use txt file,
      you are NOT allowed to use this MikuMikuDance Model Data.
   / The copyright as a secondary work has not abandoned.
   / Sely shall not be responsible for any damage and loss that may result from using this model.

    Permission
   / Use this model for pictures and videos.
   / Use this model for icon of Twitter and various SNS.
   / Editing this model for the use to create your videos and pictures is allowed.
       Accordance with the terms.
       1, Change of colors and textures. (adding bones OK)
       2, Change of costume. (However, editing this model into a base model is forbidden.)
       3, Change of size.
       4, Change of breast size is DENIED.
       5, When the edited data is distributed, it clarifies that it is reconstruction of the model made by Sely.
           more, be sure to attach this readme file and to write Sely and the person that made a change.

    Prohibitions
   / You may distribute this MMD Model Data, ONLY if you have made edits to her.
      Do not distribute her if you have not made any changes.
   / Do not take this Model apart. You are not allowed to create another MMD Model by using parts of this MMD Model Data.
      (For example, do not take this Model's hair and put it on a different Model.)
   / Do not use this MMD Model for works which include obscene, grotesque, and violent content.
   / You are NOT permitted to sell this MMD Model data in ANY format, whether digital or in print.
      This MMD Model data may only be used for non-profit purposes. Do not use this MMD Model data for commercial purposes.

   / When judgment of permission or prohibition cannot be performed, please consult by Twitter.

 \ If you find any works on a NON-JAPANESE website which do not follow these rules,
    I would greatly appreciate it if you can ask that individual to delete that video and image.


         Pass:Gummy
     Thank you for using.
-------------------------
    Model created by: Sely
    Twitter : @Selycaress
-------------------------